

# **Artur Yaroshenko**

#### WEB SOFTWAER DEVELOPER

## SUMMARY

My name is Artur. I've been doing web development for more than 7 years. I mostly write in typescript, python and golang. In my spare time I do open source contributing and run a small blog - https://du-blog.ru.

During my practice I've dealt with big enterprise projects as well as small startups, which I had to finish as prototype as soon as possible. My soft skills are: communication skills, curiosity and pragmatic approach, desire to learn and study. I love working in a team, but I can also work independently. To achieve my goals I use planning methods, Objective Key Result, as well as ORG mode (a format similar to markdown which allows you to structure your thoughts and objectives) and org-roam.

In my work I try to use only the best practices and tools, which allow me to achieve my goals quickly (emacs, magit, vim keybindings etc). I also solve algorithmic problems on codewars, leetcode and other platforms. In longplaying projects I always try to write easy to read and understandable code, which is easy to maintain. Often it follows S.O.L.I.D principles as well as some elements of extreme programming (it depends on the project, I prefer to use TDD and pair programming in complex projects). I try to find a balance between the time spent on the task and the result which can potentially save me a lot of development effort.

I prefer to write reusable and versatile code which is open to extensions and closed to changes.

## CONTACT

- artawower@protonmail.com
- +995 595 437 479
- grurwebdev.com
- artawower
- artawower

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Freelance web developer

EMPLOYER 2015-2019

Worked in a variety of frameworks and teams. Most interesting:

- -Developing a log aggregation system and network vulnerability analytics. (Django Rest Framework, Vue2, Clickhouse, Postgresql, Echarts)
- -Personal account development for working with betting data (Golang, React)
- -Developing the system of collecting stock quotes from NASDAQ, visualization and notification system (NestJS, React, Golang, Nats, Clickhouse)
- Frontend Developer

WAVE ACCESS 2019-2021

Developed projects for the corporate segment, as well as public companies.

- -Government services. The development of the client side of the Russian Federation citizen information management portal, the development of a dynamic website builder for the manual creation of regional agencies and websites. (Angular)
- -Development of a service to monitor and detect environmental pollution (Angular, NodeJs)
- -Development of a universal CAT system combining several existing formats for plotting and graphing (Vue 2, Python)
- -Development of FitBit and Quora Ring health monitoring service (Angular, Python, Django)
- Frontend Developer

PALEX GROUP 2021-now

Developing an application to check grammar and syntax when translating between different language pairs (Angular, PWA, SPA, indexeddb)

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's of computer science and computer engineering

VLADIMIR STATE UNIVERSITY

2015-2019

## SKILLS

100%

Typescript

React

Postgresql

100%

**Angular** 

100% Golang

(1

100%

vue2/3

50% MongoDb

100%

Emacs

100%

Python

75%

Django



PWA/SPA